import { Question } from "../contestantControls";

export const kiwiQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 106,
    question: "What biblical story is the binding of Isaac loosely inspired by?",
    options: ["Abraham", "Samson", "Cain"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 107,
    question: "What game engine was the original Isaac built on?",
    options: ["Unity", "Adobe Flash", "Source Engine"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 108,
    question: "What is the name suffix of the 2014 remake of the game?",
    options: ["Unchained", "Ascended", "Rebirth"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 109,
    question: "What expansion introduced the final DLC content to the latest game in 2021?",
    options: ["Repentance", "Relent", "Sorrow"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 110,
    question: "What type of game genre does Isaac belong to?",
    options: ["Boomer Shooter", "Roguelike", "Roguelite"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 111,
    question: "Which boss is a giant version of a normal fly?",
    options: ["Lord of the Flies", "The Duke of Flies", "The King of Flies"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 112,
    question: "What is the primary form of attack for Isaac and most characters?",
    options: ["Tears", "Goop", "Slashing"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 113,
    question: "What is the name of the final boss in the Cathedral?",
    options: ["Isaac", "Dogma", "Gemini"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 114,
    question: "What happens to Isaac at the very start of the game’s cutscene?",
    options: ["Mom dies", "He gets abandoned", "Hides in the basement"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 115,
    question: "Which boss is a giant living pile of excrement?",
    options: ["Dingle", "Poopy", "Gurdy"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 116,
    question: "What type of door requires you to take damage to enter?",
    options: ["A checkpoint", "A curse room door", "A bossfight entrance"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 117,
    question: "Which of the following items does not give you the ability to fly?",
    options: ["Dead Dove", "Holy Grail", "Dead Bird"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 118,
    question: "What video game is the HUD of Binding of Isaac based on?",
    options: ["The legend of Zelda", "Earthbound", "Pokemon"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 119,
    question: "What do green mushrooms represent?",
    options: ["Temporary super speed", "Extra life", "Power up"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 120,
    question: "Which of these items does NOT boost health?",
    options: ["Magic Scab", "IV Bag", "Maggy’s Bow"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  }
];